

# **MUHAMMAD YUSUF SEPTIAN**

 $085786214593 \ | \ yusufseptian \\ 39@gmail.com \ | \ www.linkedin.com/in/yusuf-septian \ | \ https://github.com/yusufseptian$ 

Muntilan, Magelang, Central Java, Indonesia

I have experience as a fullstack web developer, system analyst, and as a project lead on several software development projects. I have more than two years of experience. I master the PHP and Javascript programming languages and master the Codeigniter and Laravel frameworks. besides me too, I have good analytical and problem solving skills. Apart from that, I like learning new things and am easy to adapt.

### **Work Experiences**

#### PT. Kedata Indonesia Digital - Yogyakarta

Oct 2021 - Dec 2021

Fullstack Web Developer

Kedata is one stop services to some big data research, workshop, and machine learning facility to analytic data.

• Participated in building the project "Smart Office Tubaba" aplication in the Tulang Bawang Barat district government. this website was built using the Codeigniter framework and i joined the development team with the role of Fullstack Web Developer

### Dysania Dev - Magelang, Indonesia

Nov 2022 - Present

Fullstack Web Developer & Project Lead

- Built a software development effort with the team and me as the project lead.
- Conduct weekly meetings with the team for system development progress reportsCreated landing page of dysania dev company in static website.
- Lead in the development of online attendance system at SMAN Hargeulis Indramayu, Indonesia. this system is based on Website.
- As a project lead in building a student ledger system of SMK YPKK 1 Sleman based on website and using Codeigniter framework.
- Building a website-based Academic Information System of SMA PGRI 1 Gombong using Codeigniter Framework.
- · Building a website online student registration system for SMP 2 Lelea Indramayu using the Codeigniter Framework
- Developing attendance system in junior high school using QR Code scanning technology

#### Aisyiyah Muntilan Hospital - Magelang, Indonesia

Oct 2023 - Present

System Analist and IT Staff

- · Monitoring and maintaining hospital hardware
- · Monitoring private servers and hospital networks
- · build a website-based self-registration system integrated with BPJS
- · build a website-based health education and training system for hospitals

#### **Education Level**

Universitas Teknologi Yogyakarta - Jl. Siliwangi (Ringroad Utara), Jombor, Sleman, D.I. Yogyakarta 55285

Sep 2019 - Oct 2023

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science, 3.59/4.00

# Organisational Experience

### **UKM Campoerseni UTY**

May 2020 - Sep 2023

### Public Relations

Campoerseni is a student organization on campus which accommodates 5 divisions (Photography, Fine Arts, Modeling, Music and Dance).

- I have 3 years experience in the organization, with the first year as a member, the second and third years as public relations.
- I am part of the Photography Division with several experiences of events that have been carried out. Photography and Fine Arts Exhibition "HALCYON" as equipment team head
- I was also on the committee for the music concert "MTV", the Video Project "Kami Bersuara", and the Dance Performance "UNITY"

## Skills, Achievements & Other Experience

- Training and Course 

   ② (2023): Dicoding Cloud Practitioner Essentials (Belajar Dasar AWS Cloud)

- Training and Course @ (2023): Learn Basic Backend Developer
- Webinars Attended 

  (2021): The role of IoT and Cyber Security in industry 4.0

•